Natália Kals

Phone number: +64 21 027 35946
Email: nataliakals03@gmail.com
LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/nataliakals

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a person in the beginning of a career who is dedicated to professional and academic life. Highly organised, with a lot of energy and willingness to learn, experience and build knowledge. With ease of learning and relationship with work teams, I am a dynamic person and I seek to develop my professional and interpersonal skills so that I can contribute more every day to the environment in which I am working.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Assistant - Hey Peppers School

March 2022 - August 2022

Acting as an assistant at the language school, I had the opportunity to contribute in several areas, helping in the communication, administrative, financial, marketing and sales sectors.

Responsibilities:

- Welcoming students to their classes
- Assist parents and present the methodology and study plans
- Making prospecting calls to school contacts
- Finding the best study plan for each student's scenario and making sales arrangements
- Visit schools in the city in order to publicise the school and attract students
- Manage the financial area and deliver weekly reports to the school directors

Science Tutor (monitoring) - Instituto Federal Farroupilha

February 2021 - December 2021

During high school, I was invited by the teaching team to manage a group of students looking for tutoring in science. My role was to assist students in activities and facilitate learning through weekly meetings.

Responsibilities:

- Plan the content to be studied
- Developed lessons and activities for the group of students
- Create content presentations using the Microsoft Office Suite
- Provide the necessary support to students during meetings
- Apply tests to measure advancement in knowledge
- Report to teachers the status of each student

IT Technician - Click Soluções e Informática

February 2021 – April 2021

I had the opportunity to work at the company during the internship period of my IT Technician course, it was a learning period where my main role was to provide technical support for hardware and software.

Responsibilities:

- LAN-WAN network configuration
- Computer maintenance
- Microsoft Office suite installation
- Preventive maintenance of computers
- Corrective maintenance of computers

FOH - Onslow

April 2023 - June 2023

During my English studies, I had the opportunity to work at the Onslow restaurant, where I worked as a runner, delivering meals to customers' tables.

Responsibilities:

- Efficiently delivering meals to customers' tables, ensuring timely and accurate service
- Maintaining a clean and organised work environment, including clearing tables and resetting them for the next guests
- Demonstrating a positive and friendly attitude to create a welcoming atmosphere for diners
- Adapting quickly to changing circumstances and high-pressure situations during peak dining hours

Kitchen Hand/Barista - Espresso Workshop Britomart

August 2023 - February 2024

At the Espresso Workshop Britomart, I undertook a variety of fundamental roles to ensure the efficient operation of the establishment. As a kitchen assistant, my main task was to prepare food and assemble dishes. In customer service, I took orders and provided detailed information about the menu, aiming to provide a positive experience for the customers. Additionally, I had the opportunity to deepen my knowledge in the barista area, where I developed skills in coffee preparation, including catering to each customer's individual preferences.

EDUCATION

IT Technician

Instituto Federal Farroupilha - Brazil February 2017 – July 2021

English Language

NZLC - New Zealand Language Centres - Auckland, New Zealand November 2022 – May 2023

Full Stack Developer certification

RocketSeat - Brazil March 2024 – December 2024